[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the dogs that attacked the butler in The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "Lafayette and Napoleon", "incorrect_answers": ["Boneparte and Gilligan", "Gilbert and Lafayette", "Napoleon and Boneparte"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This modern amphitheatre, officially opened in 1922, on the site of a natural amphitheatre formerly known as the Daisy Dell, is used primarily for music performances.", "correct_answer": "Hollywood Bowl", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Rocks", "None of these", "Isirium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2003 movie starring Eliza Dushku sported the tag line, Its the last one youll ever take.", "correct_answer": "Wrong Turn", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabin Fever", "Saw", "Jeepers Creepers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first passenger car of this Japanese car make was built in 1936. The brand also operates Lexus and Scion.", "correct_answer": "Toyota", "incorrect_answers": ["Honda", "Nissan", "Yamaha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Crow, Erics call sign is a stylized bird, presumably a crow. How did Eric make his call-sign after killing Tin-Tin?", "correct_answer": "In blood, on the wall", "incorrect_answers": ["Carving it into his chest", "In blood, on the ground", "In fire, on the ground"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This rhythm and blues song from 1951 is claimed by the owner of Sun Records, Sam Phillips, to be the first rock and roll song.", "correct_answer": "Rocket 88", "incorrect_answers": ["Roll With me Henry", "Rock Around the Clock", "Its All Right Baby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What makes time travel possible according to fictional character Doc Brown?", "correct_answer": "The Flux Capacitor", "incorrect_answers": ["Reaching speeds of 100mph", "Plutonium", "Electricity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the paradisal land under the sea in the 1968 animated film Yellow Submarine?", "correct_answer": "Pepperland", "incorrect_answers": ["Paperland", "Beatland", "Merryland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What can microexpressions, a type of tiny fleeting facial expressions, help you understand about the person you are talking with?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Their real attitude towards the topic", "Their emotional state", "Whether they are telling the truth or not"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is its natural habitat of the smallest bird on the planet, the Bee Hummingbird?", "correct_answer": "Cuba and the Isle of Youth", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "All of these", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Amelia Earhart, the first woman to fly solo across the Atlantic, was born in what city and state?", "correct_answer": "Atchison, Kansas", "incorrect_answers": ["Omaha, Nebraska", "Louisville, Kentucky", "New York City, New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Broccoli originated in this country about 2000 years ago.", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Spain", "Greece"]}]